Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
obtained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
His dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuits
of dreams greater than
they ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come forward and bring us along,
all your hopes and dreams,
together we will find a greeting
that we're looking for, one piece.
The hump is left behind.
It'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide.
Raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place.
That the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary.
Till someone proves it real.
Through it all, through all the trouble.
And through the heartache.
And through the pain.
I know that I will be there.
To stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come forward and pray along.
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything.
That we will explore.
There is silence.
For you.
If you want to be my friend?
We are!
We are on the cruise!
Praise Alabasta!
Yay!
Take care on your voyage!
Didi-chan looked like she was
having a fine time, didn't she?
She must have been feeling
like a pirate again.
Just when I thought she'd started
to act like a real princess.
Yes, this is Head.
We will now proceed to escort
the Nefaltari safe to Mary Jo's.
Princess Vivi!
Please get down from there at once!
The ocean breeze feels so wonderful.
Princess Vivi!
What if a monstrous bird were to sweep
down from the sky and abduct you?
What if there were a sniper
lurking in wait to take your life?
What if a meteor fell from the sky?
Princess Vivi traveled
with pirates, remember?
There are marines
standing right next to us.
You worry too much.
Cough. Cough.
Please do not strain
yourself, Your Majesty.
If you are feeling unwell,
we can turn back at any time.
No, I am alright.
Ever since that day when I met Nico Robin,
I've had some questions that I would
like to ask of the world government.
Is this about the poneglyphs?
Too many enemies in the way of my dream I
must attend this reverie no matter what.
And if fate will allow it I would
very much like to know what it was.
That the king of the house of
Nefertari did to the world long ago.
Ma! Ma! Ma! Ma! Ma!
Honestly, will you stop
this madness, Princess Vivi?
Father, how are you feeling?
Hmm, I have certainly felt better.
Perhaps I do not have much longer.
If only my daughter
were to take a husband.
We have received a veritable
mountain of photographs from suitors.
Turn them all away.
Congratulations on your recent
coronation, your majesty!
We hope you find
everything to your liking.
This hotel was built for the
sole use of royal personages.
on their journey to the
reverie once every four years.
It is not, not, not bad.
Isn't that right, dear?
Well, it is fairly ordinary.
This view of Gold Roger's execution
platform is charming enough.
Well, then have a wonderful stay.
We hope you rest well.
Yes, yes.
Be gone from my sight, you
irritating pieces of trash.
King Stella!
In countries the world over,
there are stirrings afoot,
for an event held only once
every four years approaches.
An event held at the center of
the world in Marijua itself.
The Reverie, a council of kings.
At this, the greatest of all councils,
the rulers of fifty
kingdoms gather in one place
to discuss and debate
matters of global importance,
and decide upon their
plans for the future.
But when these bunning and
off-centric rulers come face-to-face,
matters never seen to proceed
as smoothly as one may hope.
The war is over,
and Tang Chin Jiao, that is to
say, Tang Sai, has yet to return.
I fear that we will miss Reverie,
and we have many matters to discuss.
Ma-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Scar Kingdom, don't make me laugh.
Now, how best to put that buffoon
Dalton in his place? What?
What's that unappreciated face for?
I'm saying I'll join you
as your ship's doctor.
You're happy, right?
Really? I can come?
You can be my attendant, how about it?
I'd love to.
Thank you, Viola-san.
Oh, this sounds exciting.
Ah, King Rick.
I already turned down
my battleship escort.
Say, why don't we travel
to the Holy Land together?
Oh, do you think this
is some kind of holiday?
And what's wrong with that?
I'm sorry. I can't.
I'm too scared.
Luffy-sama made a promise to me.
He promised that when we meet again,
he would take me to the
real forest on the surface.
And I don't doubt Luffy-kun
will take you anywhere you wish.
But this isn't a long journey.
We are only traveling to
Mary Joy, directly above.
Oh, this won't do it.
Father, shall we not just let
Shirahoshi sit this one out, Merde?
Yeah, she doesn't need to go in person.
We have plenty of signatures for our
petition to re-locate Fishman Island. Mambo!
To leave her behind will
be not allowed to say
that we do not trust the
humans or want them to.
Shirahoshi, what did the
Star Hat Pirates teach you?
This council is our chance to
fulfill our mother Otohime's wish.
Let us go together.
A little of a starboard.
Sure, like this.
A little more.
Hey, hey, hey, put a
little more effort into it.
Are you trying to sink us? Shut up.
If you hadn't leapt off from
the top of Zoe like that,
we wouldn't be all so
rattled, idiot. Thank you.
I am reflecting on how
wonderful it is to be alive.
I won't forget this.
Wow!
We're really on the sea!
This big, heavy boat is
just floating along! Huh?
What are you doing on the board?
Carrot! Yoo-hoo!
Carrot? Why are you?
I decided to come along.
Crush!
Gar! Nami!
Gar!
Chopper! Crush!
Baron Corpse!
Crush!
I'm afraid we'll just have
to turn this ship around.
Don't turn back now!
Wanda will be really angry.
I just wanted to go on
an adventure for once.
This isn't a game.
Please, I'll do anything.
Just take me with you.
I won't get in the way.
Look, I've brought lunch.
Some juice, a snack.
Spare clothes, and.
The ocean really is.
A wonderland.
It's not a land at all.
It's the opposite of land.
I've never been on a sleepover before.
Oh well, it'll be fine.
Yep, thank you. I'll be.
Why are you eating my carrot?
My neck!
Pat her head, Luffy!
That was close.
I almost died.
Luffy almost got killed.
Well, she's used to a fight.
Where the...
When did you get all the
way up there, Pedro-san?
I'm hungry.
Let's have food.
Somebody make food.
Uh-oh, you're all hopeless.
I'll go make something
to keep watch, will you?
It'll cost you 5,000 penny each.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
That's like all of my allowance.
What are you suggesting?
This is a pretty big headline.
I'll make it.
A location shrouded in mystery
for decades is finally discovered.
Baltigo, headquarters of the
Revolutionary Army, lies in ruins.